(Penny(entering):)Hi. Did Sheldon
change the Wi-Fi password again?
Uh, yeah, it's "Penny already eats
our food, she can pay for Wi-Fi."
(Leonard:)No spaces.
Okay. What makes you think you
can get me to stop using your wi-Fi?
(Sheldon:)I believe that you're capable
of great change.
(Sheldon:)Like, when I finally got you
to stop saying "Valentime's Day."
- Wanna hear something weird?
- Sure.
(Sheldon:)In the year 2000...
...Pope John Paul ll was named
an honorary Harlem Globetrotter.
(Leonard:)What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)You asked Penny if she wanted
to hear something weird.
Well, yeah, because I have
something weird to tell her.
(Sheldon:)Oh. I thought it was a game.
- What's yours?
- There's this guy, Jimmy Speckerman.
He used to torment me
in high school.
(Leonard:)He sent me a message
through Facebook.
(Leonard:)- He's in town and wants to have drinks.
- Okay, Penny.